# MAURICIO CÁCERES LOBOS



## CONTACT

Vestervaenget 10 Vaer, 1 Tilst, Aarhus, Denmark. Salto del Agua 351, Placiila, Valparaíso, Chile

+569 32889517 / +4550292253

mauriciocaceres522012@gmail.com

# TRAININGS

Offshore
Onshore
Cable Car
Minig
Arboriculture
Industry
Civil Works
Rescue

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish
English
Portuguese
Danish

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have been working vertically for a decade in rope access. I worked in the industrial area, maintaining wind turbines in Denmark, and also worked as a rescuer in thermoelectric plants in Chile. I periodically carry out slope reinforcement work in Andorra. My biggest sacrifice was working in the Emirates at 43 degrees Celsius.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

04/2021 - 04/2022

Vertical Operator, **VESTAS**, Herlev. **Denmark** 

#### Responsibilities:

 Operational service of cleaning and maintenance of wind turbines.

03/2020 - 05/2021

Vertical Operator, REBTEKNIKEREN, Copenhagen, Denmark

#### Responsibilities:

- Logistic service and realization of quotations in new projects.
- Supervision of vertical works and difficult access.
- Planned rescue service for, work at height and confined spaces.

#### **EDUCATION**

International tourist administrator, INACAP

University. Valparaíso, Chile.

2004 – 2009

2000 - 2004

Electromechanical Intermediate level, Mixed Private School.

Santiago, Chile.

#### REFERENCES

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC8NriOhAzrapVhbsp2CQnpQ

YouTube Channel

https://www.linkedin.com/in/realmentemauricio/

LinkedIn

